(Wyatt:)Says he loves you.
(Leonard:)What?
(Penny:)I see.
(Wyatt:)The whole thing's
bull squirt, huh?
(Wyatt:)Well, that's very disappointing.
(Penny:)Bye.
(Penny:)Oh, hey.
(Leonard:)There's been something I've
been meaning to tell you.
(Wyatt:)I can't believe you would
lie to me like that.
(Leonard:)Just for the record, I did not
want to be a part of this.
(Wyatt:)I'll get to you in a minute.
(Leonard:)No hurry.
(Wyatt:)That my own daughter thinks
I don't love her enough
(Wyatt:)to support her no matter
what choices she makes--
(Wyatt:)well, that hurts me deeply.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, Daddy...
Let me finish.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Wyatt:)I thought we were
past the days
(Wyatt:)when you would try
to pull the wool over my eyes.
(Wyatt:)Telling me the baggie in your
underwear drawer is potpourri?
(Wyatt:)And the pee stick
in your bathroom
(Wyatt:)is to check for diabetes?
(Penny:)You know, I'm sorry.